

Javad Adib







Full Stack PHP Developer, Software Engineer

Lives 15+ years with code and debugging as a programmer. Build 7+ infrastructure of multi-million dollar scalable projects from scratch. Earn valuable knowledge via collaboration with specialists. Software engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the IT, Fintech, blockchain, eCommerce industries. A learner who knows how to learn. Open-source enthusiast.







02/2022 v6.5.0

Professional Experience

Founder, CEO, and Full Stack Developer

libres Iran (4 years 6 months) 10/2017 - present

- Provide cloud infrastructure to 1,000+ businesses, integrated eCommerce solution with website, app, PoS software, CMS, CRM, accounting software, ticketing system, form builder.
- Joined the bug bounty program and introduced a new WAF that filters and monitors 99% of the attacks.
- Launched an automated app factory that generated a native android shopping app without coding in less than 10 minutes.

Founder, CEO, and Software Engineer

Ermile Iran (4 years 8 months) 06/2015 - 12/2019

- Raised \$1M from Angel investor, spearheaded a 15 member cross-functional team to create a Sarshomar that gained about 1M users just a month after launch.
- Constructed the most comprehensive private educational management system in Iran, which serves four organizations, 500,000+ students, 2,000+ teachers.
- Built Siftal UI framework, Dash as PHP framework with MVC pattern, 2x the development speed by consolidated SPA.

Web UI/UX Designer

Freelancer (6 years 11 months) 09/2008 - 06/2015

- Designed, developed 40+ WordPress websites, user experience, communicated with dozens of customers, including universities, companies, government centers, celebrities.
- Strengthened negotiation skills, mastered sales skills, optimized speed of 10+ websites, achieved high SEO rank.

Computer Lecturer

Teacher (15+ years) 06/2006 - (continued)

- Taught 2000+ students in web technologies courses, ICDL in 4 universities, vocational colleges, private classes.
- Created, published tens of hours of unique free web, office video tutorials, which has led to the acquisition of skills by thousands of Persian speakers around the world.

Volunteer work

DevOps and Front-End Developer

Khadije Charity Iran (4 years 4 months) 12/2017 - 03/2022

• Developed the website, all the software infrastructure, accelerated fulfill the wishes of 110,000+ people.

Software Solutions for Business Expert

WorldSkills Iran Iran (5 years 4 months) 06/2010 - 08/2015

 Tutored, train three talents who won silver, two bronze medals in national competitions; Held the national team camp to attend WorldSkills Sao Paulo 2015.

<u>Languages</u>

English Fluent C1 Persian Native

Education

M.S. in IT Management

Azad University Tehran, Iran 2015 - 2022

B.S. in Computer Software Engineering

Azad University Nour, Iran 2008 - 2014

<u>Skills</u>



Fully Proficient Web Technology HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP Language C, C++, C#, VB.NET, Node.js, TypeScript, Python, Bash Web Service SOAP, RESTful API, GraphQL

Back-end Web Framework Laravel, Symfony

Data Structure and Database MySQL, SQL Server, JSON, YAML

Frontend JS Library Alpine.js, React, Vue.js, Angular, jQuery

Build Tools Sass, Grunt, Gulp, Gradle, Webpack

CSS Framework Tailwind, Bootstrap, Semantic UI, Materialize

Backend Web Server Nginx, Apache

Server Configuration Framework, UI cPanel, DirectAdmin

OS Windows, Ubuntu, Debian, CentOS, macOS, VMware ESXi

CI/CD Container Docker, Kubernetes

Test-driven development - TDD PHPUnit

Microsoft Office Specialist Word, Excel, Access, PowerPoint, VBA Graphic Design Tools Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Figma

Awards and Honors

Membership	Iran
National Elites Foundation	2013
T D . O . T	

The Best Corporate, Tourism Website

5th Iran Web Festival

2012

5th Iran Web Festival 2012 **Silver Medal** Yazd, Iran

WorldSkills Iran - IT Software Solutions for Business 2009

Medallion for Excellence Mashhad, Iran

2008

WorldSkills Iran - IT Software Applications